[Music]
[Música]
H
H
ch Oh
ch Oh
[Music]
[Música]
H [Music]
H
ha
ha
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah
e
e
al al al e
al
[Music]
[Música]
k
k
how bad How bad How bad How bad How bad How bad How bad How
qué mal Qué mal Qué mal Qué mal Qué mal
bad first time I
Qué mal Qué mal Qué mal primera vez que
do a live on the main channel
hago un directo en el canal principal
with this program okay normally like
con este programa vale normalmente como
just doing the live shows always when
solo hacer los directos siempre cuando
they are on the main channel they are special live shows
son en el canal principal son directos
no and I do it with the Stream
especiales no y lo hago con el Stream
Well I had to configure the whole BS
Pues he tenido que configurar todo el BS
okay for this you're telling me that
vale para esto me estáis diciendo que me
Fran has done a raid on me but how is he
ha hecho una raide el Fran pero cómo me
going to do a raid on me I mean he knew how to
va a hacer una raide o sea ha sabido
do it Ah analog analog no I mean he
hacerlo Ah analógica analógica no O sea
sent the gang like
ha mandado la peña en plan
analogously no analogously no Hey well
analógicamente no analógicamente no Oye
a hug Fran look now he's
pues un abrazo Fran mira ahora me está
talking to me walking to the people over there a
hablando andado a la gente para allí un
kiss handsome a kiss later I'll see what you
beso guapo un beso luego veo qué es lo
've told because he caught me
que has contado porque me ha cogido
picking up the boy but I saw that you've
recogiendo al chico pero he visto que
been telling some little thing I'll
has estado contando alguna cosilla lo
see  then in telesalseo surely
veré luego en telesalseo seguramente
Okay but you don't know that you can do
Vale pero no sabes que se puede hacer
a ride that no no no way no I mean he did it he did it he
una ride eso no no ni de coña no O sea
forced us okay
lo ha hecho lo ha hecho nos obligó vale
but he did it in an analog way not
pero lo ha hecho en plan analógico no a
the old way come over there go over
la antigua pasaros para allá iros por
there okay I understand a kiss handsome
allí vale lo entiendo un beso guapo
Thank you very much Today there's a
Muchísimas gracias Hoy se viene un
special coming up a live show in which I'm going to give
especial un directo en el que voy a dar
an exclusive
una exclusiva
and And well the truth is that [ __ ] it's going to
y Y bueno pues la verdad que [__] va a
be an exclusive that's going to be really
ser una exclusiva que va a estar muy
good during the night the information is going to be expanded
bien durante la noche se va a ampliar la
Okay and the protagonists will
información Vale y los protagonistas
give absolute details of this this
darán detalles absolutos de esta de esta
bomb okay because this is a bomb and I
bomba vale porque esto es una bomba y
have to tell you First things first
tengo que deciros lo Primero lo primero
okay the first the first the first
vale la primera la primera la primera
the first information and the first
la primera información y la primera
clue that I have to give you about the
pista que os tengo que dar sobre la
exclusive that we're going to give Well I don't know if
exclusiva que vamos a dar Pues no sé si
with a goal of likes with a goal of
con una meta de likes con una meta de
subscriptions I don't know how to do it or
suscripciones no sé cómo hacerlo o
waiting a while is that I had to
esperándome un rato es que he tenido que
do it live at this time well
hacer directo a esta hora pues
practically because I have an appointment with the
prácticamente porque tengo cita con la
nutritionist I have to leave at like
nutricionista me tengo que ir como a las
4 or 5 so Did I do it now or not Let's
4 a las 5 entonces Os lo hací ahora o no
see Yesterday I was tying up loose ends  the
A ver Ayer estuve atando Cabos por la
night when I finished the live at the
noche cuando terminé el directo en la
salsería and And well, I have received
salsería y Y bueno pues me ha llegado
some information, I have received some
una información me ha llegado una
information that I think I am the first, I
información que creo que soy el primer
think I am the first youtuber streamer
creo que soy el primer youtuber streamer
in Spain to know it and it is
de España en conocerla y es una
information that starting today is going to
información que a partir de hoy va a
change
cambiar
absolutely How would you
absolutamente Cómo se
say this information I am going to give you
diría esta información os voy a dar
now okay this information that I am going to
ahora okay esta información que os voy a
give you today is going to change absolutely everything Let's
dar hoy va a cambiar absolutamente todo
see wouldn't it be if I say the lobby we
el A ver no sería si decir el lobby
could say the Lori the the lobby we
podríamos decir el Lori el el el lobby
could say the lobby this
podríamos decir el lobby esta
information that I am going to say this
información que voy a decir esta
information that always goes on your
información que va siempre en vuestro
favorite gossip channel of course
canal favorito de salseo por supuesto
where the news comes out first and and
donde salen primero las noticias y y el
your favorite gossip channel okay
vuestro canal favorito de chisme vale
this information that is going to come out here today is
esta información que va a salir aquí hoy
going to change absolutely the whole
va a cambiar absolutamente toda la
story I
historia o
mean it's a
sea es una
bomb the Lori the lazy Lori the
bomba el Lori el Lori perezoso el Lori
lazy Lori eh it is a bomb it is going to change
perezoso eh es una bomba va a cambiar la
history it is going to change history as you
historia va a cambiar la historia tal y
know it until today of the
como la conocéis hasta el día de hoy del
internet lobby and the
lobby de internet y de la
elite the elite will no longer be the same
élite la élite ya no va a ser la misma
after this news that I am going to give
después de esta noticia que voy a dar
but I don't know how let's see I am going to wait for
pero no sé cómo a ver voy a esperar que
people to come in because  I just
vaya entrando la gente porque acabo de
started the live okay we're only 12
abrir el directo vale apenas llevamos 12
minutes in and most of the time it's
minutos y y la mayoría de del tiempo es
music okay but it's true that I'm
música vale pero sí que es verdad que
going to wait a little bit what happens is that I don't
voy a esperar un poco lo que pasa que no
know what it does I don't know if it sets a goal for
sé que hacé no sé si pone una meta de
likes what do I know to see if people feel like it
likes yo que sé para ver si la gente
saying the information I do
tiene ganas de que diga la información
n't know if Set a goal for likes
no sé si Pon una meta de likes de
comments subscriptions or what the
comentarios de suscripciones o qué la
truth is I have no idea I think I'm going to just
verdad no tengo ni idea creo que lo voy
let it go whenever I
a soltar y punto en el momento que me
feel like it okay well listen to me there are
apetezca vale bueno escúchame faltan
1000 subscribers left on this channel
faltan 1000 suscriptores en este canal
to reach 600,000 we could set
para llegar a 600.000 podríamos poner
that goal eh a thousand and a bit are missing we could
esa meta eh mil y poco faltan podríamos
set that that goal we reached
poner esa esa meta llegamos a los
600,000 boom I drop the bomb and I'm and I'm
600.000 pum suelto la bomba y me y me
going and I'm
voy y me
going I'm going quietly to the
voy me voy tranquilito a la
nutritionist pim pom Pam and and I've left
nutricionista pim pom Pam y y he dejado
here All the all afternoon no No man
aquí Toda la toda la tarde no No hombre
Chari but to ask ask for members like to
Chari pero pedir pedir miembros como
ask for [ __ ] no practically So I'm
pedir perras no prácticamente Entonces
not going to ask for [ __ ] for this bomb I'm
no voy a pedir perras por esta bomba
just going to give it and and outside
simplemente la voy a dar y y fuera
no I think that the goal of the
no yo creo que la meta de los de los
subscribers  it's okay to reach
suscriptores está bien llegar a los
600,000 and we'll go easy on the
600.000 y nos vamos tranquilitos con los
600,000 and now that they're talking about me
600.000 y y ahora que que hablen de mí
all the time and all afternoon and all
todo el tiempo y todo la tarde y todo el
day and all
día y toda la
week let's see Cristina Well go to
semana a ver Cristina Pues vete a
work calmly because I think it's going to take me
trabajar tranquila porque creo que voy a
a while eh I'm going to take it
tardar un ratito eh Me lo voy a tomar
easy in fact I'm going to give you a I'm going to
calma de hecho os voy a dar una os voy a
give you a clue okay I'm going to give you a
dar una pista vale os voy a dar una
tip Well today there was supposed to be a video on
piza Bueno hoy tenía que haber vídeo en
the main channel but the editor told me
el canal principal pero el editor me ha
that he's going to work harder okay And
dicho que se lo va a currar más vale Y
then the video is going to be uploaded the video of the
entonces el vídeo se va a subir el vídeo
Main Channel today is going to be uploaded
del Canal principal de hoy se va a subir
tomorrow okay it's a response to someone
mañana vale es una respuesta a alguien
that I think that I think that sometimes you have to
que yo creo que yo creo que algunas
respond not always you don't respond you don't
responder no siempre no se responde no
respond I think I think that you have to
se responde yo creo que yo creo que hay
respond on some occasion from time
que responder en alguna ocasión de vez
to time So the video of the
en cuando Entonces el vídeo del Canal
Main Channel will be tomorrow tomorrow so that it is
principal estará mañana mañana para que
more beautiful more I don't know the
esté más más bonito más yo que sé el
editor told me
editor me ha dicho
that I'm going to give you a
eso os voy a dar una
clue I'm going to give you a clue
pista os voy a dar una pista
although I have put This title and this
aunque he puesto Este título y esta
thumbnail the one you are
miniatura la que estáis
seeing in  the moment we drop the
viendo en el momento que soltemos la
bomb, the title of the thumbnail
bomba el título de la miniatura la
we have to change
tenemos que cambiar
okay
vale Por
Why Because the title well the title Yes
qué Porque el título bueno el título Sí
the title yes yes it agrees no with what we are
el título si si concuerda no con lo que
going to talk about in the live but the
vamos a hablar en el directo pero la
thumbnail no the thumbnail has nothing to
miniatura no la miniatura no tiene nada
do with the bomb it is not about that the
que ver con la bomba no es de ese el
topic is about a much
tema es de uno muchísimo más
stronger one it is a much stronger topic it
fuerte es un tema muchísimo más fuerte
is an exclusive from people that you
es una exclusiva de gente a la que
appreciate or
aprecias o
know it is an exclusive about people that I
conoces es una exclusiva sobre gente que
know it is exclusive that the moment
conozco es exclusiva que en el momento
that I drop it now the whole
que yo la suelte ahora va a estar todo
internet is going to be talking about This
internet hablando de Esto
okay yesterday he said that several streamers knew this
vale ayer dijo que esto lo sabían varios
but not Spanish I think
streamers pero no españoles creo que
Spanish I would say that Spanish I am the
españoles Yo diría que españoles soy el
first let's say I think the only one who
primero vamos creo que el único que lo
knows But I think that I think that Spanish
sabe Pero creo que creo que españoles
I am the only one who knows I think that
soy el único que que lo sabe Creo que se
now all the Spanish streamers are going to find out about
van a enterar ahora todos los streamers
this
españoles a raíz de este directo de esta
bomb okay m let's see of course I can't
bomba vale m a ver claro es que no se me
think of anyone close
ocurre nadie cercano
Spanish let's see I know me cona that they
español a ver yo sé me cona que lo
know less than the fingers of the hands on
saben menos de los dedos de las manos en
the other side of the pond
el otro lado del Charco
okay less people know on the
vale lo saben menos personas de los
fingers of both hands but on the other
dedos de las dos manos pero en el otro
side of the
lado del
pond okay  it
Charco vale
's national or international news international
es una noticia nacional o internacional
international that will be great no In fact I have to
internacional que será padre no De hecho
cut my ponytail I would
tengo que cortarme la coleta
like Well yesterday we were
me gustaría Bueno ayer estuvimos
talking on the main channel on the
hablando en el canal principal en el
main channel no in the salseria
canal principal de no en la salsería
we were talking about this topic of
estuvimos hablando sobre el tema este de
auron okay I'm not going to comment much
de auron vale no voy a comentar mucho
more on this topic Okay practically if
más sobre este tema Ok prácticamente si
you were watching yesterday's live
estuvisteis viendo el directo de ayer
Here's a little dig from auron curious
Aquí hay una pullita de auron curiosa
little dig from Puerto Rico handsome Send him
pullita desde Puerto Rico guapo Mándale
a greeting tell him not to be a liar or a
un saludo a dile que no sea mentirosa ni
liar a greeting to Jennifer do
embustera un saludito para Jennifer que
n't be a liar and a liar Opa
no sea mentirosa y embustera Opa mucho
you ask for the truth a lot you ask King mother
pides la verdad mucho pide Rey madre
God Okay about this practically what You're
Dios Bueno sobre esto prácticamente lo
going to know Surely I think
que Vais a saber Seguramente yo creo que
that auron in the next few hours I don't know if he
que auron en las próximas horas no sé si
will do it today or he will do it tomorrow or when
lo hará hoy o lo hará mañana o cuándo
okay because today today the news is this
vale porque hoy hoy la noticia es esta
So I think that probably auron will
Entonces yo creo que probablemente auron
now
ahora
do a live broadcast simply announcing
hará un directo comunicando simplemente
the breakup Okay and then that live broadcast of
la ruptura Ok y luego ese directo de
auron is going to be
auron va a quedar
completely overshadowed
completamente ensombrerado
I think that Auro the only thing he's going to
yo creo que Auro lo único que va a
comment on is the breakup because
comentar es la la ruptura porque yo
knowing him I would say that he's going to
conociéndolo diría que este se lo va a
eat this one  with potato what about Gemita and it doesn't
comer con patata lo de gemita y no
work she's not going to tell the truth okay but I'll
va no va a contar la verdad vale pero la
tell you the truth the truth is
verdad os la cuento yo la verdad son
Okay okay let me tell it
Bueno ya bueno que lo cuent yo Es que
Yesterday de Auron's own brother didn't come he wasn't
ayer el propio hermano de de auron no
very discreet he wasn't very
fue no fue muy discreto no fue muy
discreet Auron's own brother
discreto el propio hermano de auron
posted a photo there of one of a goat
publicó una foto ahí de uno de una cabra
with really big horns no I
con los cuernos bien grande no O sea en
mean like this has been a betrayal Okay this
plan esto ha sido una traición Ok esto
has been a betrayal on the part of
ha sido una traición por parte de de
Gemita to Auron Play also she has behaved
gemita a auron Play además se ha portado
terribly with him I mean it has been
fatal con él o sea ha sido un sin
completely senseless
sentido completamente
Auron has been on a roll for a few days
auron se ha pegado unos días bastante
according to what they tell me quite screwed Well
según me cuentan bastante [__] Bueno
actually he is screwed eh Actually he
de hecho que está [__] eh De hecho que
is screwed
está [__]
eh Actually he is quite screwed eh
eh De hecho que está bastante [__] eh
the brother went a bit too far well let's see
el hermano se pasó un poco bueno a ver
everyone has their own ways of communicating and
cada uno tiene su formas de comunicar y
well it hasn't been the most discreet it hasn't
bueno no ha sido la más discreta no ha
been the
sido la más discreta Pero bueno creo que
most discreet But well I think the meaning In the end it all comes to say the same thing okay I also wanted to clarify the issue of Auron's mother there are a lot of people commenting okay let's see I'm going to clarify it without getting too into the subject because the truth  It's just that
mucho en el tema porque la verdad es que
practically because of Raúl this topic,
prácticamente por por por Raúl este tema
well, I'm not going to go into it much, the truth is,
Eh pues no voy a entrar mucho la verdad
but just like I didn't go into it a couple of
Pero igual que no entré hace un par de
months ago, when they told me that
meses que ya me comunicaron que que que
Silvia was hitting on me hard, no, it's
que Silvia estaba tirándome fuerte no
not about any betrayal or
em no se trata de ninguna traición ni de
gossip, okay, uh, I've
ningún marujeo vale eh yo a mí me han
heard things that you're already insinuating
llegado cosas que ya estáis insinuando
about me or that she's saying about me, I'm not going to go
de mí o que está diciendo de mí no voy a
into it, the truth is, it seems very strong to
entrar la verdad me Me parece muy fuerte
me, it seems very strong that
Me parece muy fuerte
you're supposed to
que que se supone que tú a las personas
not treat your son well and that they
que tratan bien a tu hijo no y que
love your son or what or what, you
quieren a tu hijo o que o que tal
should have respect and appreciation for him, okay, and I
deberías tenerle respeto aprecio vale e
understand the annoyance, I understand that she was
entiendo la molestia entiendo que se
upset, okay, because of what happened, I'm not going
molestara vale por lo que pasó yo no voy
to tell what happened unless I have to
a contarlo lo que pasó a no ser que lo
clarify it or really clarify it, okay,
tenga que aclarar o requete aclarar Vale
but it's not about me being a
pero no se trata de que yo sea una
gossip or me telling off something, it's
Maruja o que yo me Chiara de algo que me
not about me as a colleague,
chivar no se trata de que yo como colega
well,
Pues
uh, I decided that I had to tell
eh decidí que tenía que comunicarle a
Auron something, that what was happening,
auron una cosa Que que estaba pasando
okay, and the thing is, I consider that there are
Vale y Y es que yo Considero que hay
things that have to stay  in the
cosas que se tienen que quedar en la en
intimacy and And practically and I don't
la intimidad y Y prácticamente e no me
regret it I'm very sorry I wouldn't
arrepiento yo lo siento mucho no me
like anyone to be angry
gustaría que nadie estuviera enfadado
with me but I don't regret it I
conmigo pero no me arrepiento yo
consider as a colleague that man be
considero como colega que tío ten
careful because this eh can go
cuidado porque esto eh puede llegar por
here it can go there and they can
aquí puede llegar por allá y te pueden
cause a huge mess they
liar un pitote de la de la [__] te
can cause a huge mess if yes they
pueden liar un pitote de la [__] si si
start to find out and above all you can't
se ponen a enterarse y sobre todo no se
talk to Twitter accounts that
puede hablar con cuentas de Twitter que
are dedicated to defaming you know then H
se dedican a a difamar sabes entonces H
surely you had your logical reasons I'm not
seguro que tenías tus razones lógicas no
telling you sincerely I was
te lo digo sinceramente yo ayer estuve
uncomfortable yesterday when this happened in the chat
incómodo cuando pasó esto en el chat
Because there is also some insinuation that
Porque además hay alguna insinuación que
is quite ugly okay for my taste and that
es bastante fea vale para mi gusto y que
is not like that obviously and that is not like that
no es así evidentemente y que no es así
okay No no no no juanma it's not that it should be it should be
vale No no no no juanma no es que
explain it and explain it would be Well look
explicarlo y explicarlo sería Pues mira
this happened and faced with this I decided that the
pasó esto y yo ante esto decidir que la
best way to react was this
la mejor manera de reaccionar era esta
for me my colleague is auron not the
para mí mi colega es auron no la
mother whoever wants to understand it, let them
madre el que lo quiera entender que lo
understand it okay No, it's not about me being a
entienda vale No no se trata de que yo
gossipmonger or anything  but I
me dedique al salseo ni nada sino que yo
saw something that I told Auron be careful be
vi una cosa que le dije a auron cuidado
careful because this could harm you
cuidado porque esto te puede perjudicar
and if this gets out if they say this or if they
e si esto sale si esto lo dicen o si
go around telling her you know what I'm telling you
esto van diciéndole sabes lo que te digo
or rather it would be getting into a topic like
o sea sería entrar en en un tema queé
that okay But well I wish
tal vale Pero bueno yo les deseo las
Silvia the best yesterday I told her I'm here
mejores a Silvia ayer se lo dije Aquí
for whatever you need Okay and and
estoy para lo que necesites Vale y y
anything well I'm really sorry that it
cualquier cosa pues lo siento mucho que
bothered you
te molestara
but I see that it was the most
pero veo que fue la La decisión más
logical and correct decision and what would they have done
lógica y correcta y que Hubieran hecho
to me too obviously because I
conmigo también evidentemente porque yo
think anyone would have done it
creo que cualquiera lo hubiera hecho
to me
conmigo
too Here I'll stay the gossip looks
también Aquí me quedaré el chisme se ve
good let's
bueno
see what what I'm going to tell you okay what I'm
a ver lo que lo que os voy a decir vale
going to tell you and I think I'm going to tell you
lo que os voy a decir y creo que ya os
and it was excessively harsh and forceful
e fue excesivamente dura y contundente
well I understand her anger I understand her
bueno entiendo su enfado entiendo su
anger but the truth is I'm
enfado pero la verdad lo siento
really sorry but I acted as one should
muchísimo pero yo actué como como se
act what happens is that uh that
actuar lo que pasa es que la eh que la
people interpret and and they go around and
la gente interpreta y y le da vueltas y
around things to interpret it
volteretas a las cosas para interpretar
as if she were me or rather what
como que a mí ella me o sea lo que ha
people have interpreted is that she  she
interpreta la gente es que a mí ella me
told me a secret and I've been
contó un secreto y que yo he ido
telling the secret around and that's
contando por ahí el secreto y así no es
never the case but not with her, I mean not with
jamás lo he hecho pero pero no con ella
her or with anyone, I mean I
o sea ni con ella ni con nadie o sea yo
know bombs but stronger than today's
sé bombas pero más fuertes que la de hoy
than what I'm going to tell you today here and
que la que os voy a contar hoy aquí y
many times I keep them to myself and I'm an
muchas veces me las callo y soy
idiot because I say damn [ __ ] I
[__] porque yo digo [__] [__]
should be a person like that
Debería ser una persona
half anonymous or half that doesn't show their
así medio anónima o medio que no muestre
face or that nobody knows who I am
la cara o que nadie sepa quién soy
imagine an account like that a twitterer a
imagínate una cuenta así un twittero un
youtuber that so doesn't show their face and [ __ ] off
youtuber que así que no enseñe la cara y
eh of the things that
a tomar por culo eh de las cosas que me
they tell me or contrast or anything pa pa pa pa you
vayan contando ni contrastar ni nada pa
know like the horns and
pa pa pa sabes como las cuern y esas
stuff like that but well things come
cosas no pero bueno las cosas vienen
as they come and and they are as they are and that's it
como vienen y y son como son y ya está
but I haven't been telling more I haven't
pero que yo no he ido contando más yo no
gone around telling anything like a gossip
he ido contando por ahí nada de chismoso
nor have I gone around betraying anyone
ni he ido por ahí traicionando a nadie
or anything like that okay I mean uh what
ni ni nada por el estilo vale o sea yo
happened was that I
eh lo que pasó fue
saw something that I had to warn
que vi una cosa que le tuve que avisar a
my friend to tell him man be
a mi colega de decirle tío esto ten
careful because he can  it can it can go it
cuidado porque puede ya puede puede ir
can fall into other hands than
puede caer en otras manos que no sea la
mine and then you know and no then
mía y entonces sabes y no entonces las
things are like that and I think that
cosas son así y yo creo que cualquier
anyone would understand that what I
persona entendería que que lo que yo
did was logical and
hice fue lo lógico y lo
sensible but the fact that they
Sensato pero vamos el hecho de que ellos
were gossips would not be
fuera un chismosos tampoco sería ninguna
news either I also tell you we are almost we are almost away from
novedad también te
reaching
llegar a los
599,000 we are almost eh from reaching
599.000 estamos a nada eh de llegar a
599,000 the moment we reach
599,000 en el momento que lleguemos a
599,000 I'll start okay
los 599,000 empiezo
I would love for you to start
va Me encantaría que me empezara
while people are subscribing
mientras que la gente se va suscribiendo
I would love for me to start eh
Me encantaría que me empezara a eh
writing in the
escribir en el
chat the names
chat los nombres
of the
de los
most famous streamers in Latin America okay
streamers más famosos de latam vale
Which would be the
Cuáles serían los más
top arij
top arij
Juan Manu
Juan Manu
Tenorio owes money to the
Tenorio le debe pasta
Treasury and he's going to pay it back little by little
Hacienda y se la va a pagar poco a poco
guys Thank you very much for having
chavales Muchísimas gracias por haber
enjoyed this live broadcast Hey the
disfrutado de este directazo Oye la
truth is that it went very well No the truth is
verdad que ha ido muy bien No la verdad
that it went no you didn't
que ha ido no no os ha
like it guys Manu Tenorio okay okay okay
gustado cabrones Manu Tenorio bueno
so we
bueno Vale pues
continue yesterday I received
seguimos ayer me llegó
one
una
news as I was telling you at the
noticia como ya os estaba diciendo al
beginning of the live I think I think
comienzo del directo Creo que creo que
I'm the first YouTuber Well I'm
soy el primer youtuber Bueno estoy
sure I'm the first
seguro que soy el primer youtuber
Spanish YouTuber who knows it
español que lo sabe
and it's news that comes from the other side of
e es una noticia que viene del otro lado
the pond it's news that comes from
del Charco es una noticia que viene de
Mexico and it
México y
's news that will be confirmed
es una noticia que se va a confirmar
tonight yesterday the truth is that I was
noche ayer la verdad es que me me
surprised that I received this because it
sorprendió que me llegara esto porque me
came to me by mistake okay
ha llegado por un error vale
sincerely I think that the person uh The one who the
sinceramente creo que la persona eh A la
way I found out okay I think
que de la forma en la que lo supe vale
that
creo que
well no no no no I'm not very I'm not
bueno no no no no estoy muy no las tengo
entirely sure okay that he knew
todas muy conmigo vale de que supiera
that this was the exclusive and the bomb
que esta era la exclusiva y la bomba
uh of the year I mean I think that this This
eh del año o sea yo creo que esto Esta
news that we're going to give here now
noticia que vamos a dar aquí ahora
absolutely changes the entire history
cambia absolutamente toda la historia
of the
del del
lobby yesterday one of these people went
lobby ayer una de estas personas acudió
to a television program in
a un programa de televisión en
Latin little by little it was getting to
latan poco a poco lo fue
know a little bit more people
Sabiendo un poquito más personas
around the circle
alrededor del círculo
and today we have it
y hoy lo tenemos
here for the followers and subscribers
aquí para los seguidores y suscriptores
of this
de este
channel Yes yes exactly uh exactly
canal Sí sí tal cual eh tal cual tal
exactly the history of the lobby as you
cual la historia del lobby tal y como la
knew it today has changed over all these
conocíais hoy cambi durante todos estos
years because there have been many rumors
años pues han habido muchos rumores
rumors of comings and
rumores de idas y
goings rumors of
venidas rumores de de
infidelities rumors even about
infidelidades rumores incluso de
orientations I mean it's that I
orientaciones O sea que es que yo ahí
believe that That one I do believe that no but it
Creo esa Esa sí que creo que no pero sí
is true that there have been at most
que es verdad que habido como mucho
Well rumors for some uh rumors
Bueno rumores para algunos eh rumores
for some for others it has not been
para algunos para otros no ha sido
rumors about infidelity and above
rumores sobre tema infidelidades y sobre
all above all above all comings and
todo sobre todo sobre todo idas y
goings no I believe that there are some
venidas no yo creo que hay algunas
people who had already realized that
personas que se habían dado cuenta ya de
these people
que esta gente
were no longer
ya no estaban
together the faces the faces were the
juntos las caras las caras eran las
faces and not only the faces were the
caras y ya no solamente las caras eran
faces but also uh one of
las caras sino que además eh una de
these people is changing their
estas personas está cambiando su
Setup and this person that we are
Setup y esta persona de la que estamos
talking about I think should change the
hablando creo que debería cambiar la
thumbnail okay let's
miniatura ya vale
change the
cambiamos la
thumbnail I am very sorry for the news
miniatura Lamento muchísimo la noticia
because it is not good obviously but I
porque no es buena evidentemente pero
have to I have to be carried today
tengo que tengo que ser portado hoy de
of bad news okay this
de malas noticias vale esto
obviously
evidentemente
uh it is confirmed Okay it is confirmed I am
eh está confirmado Okay está confirmado
sorry to be the bearer of this news
Lamento ser portador de estas noticias
eh
eh
but today in the live of I don't know which
pero hoy en el directo de no sé de cuál
of the two okay surely in one of
de los dos vale seguramente en uno de
the two the divorce of
los dos se va a anunciar el divorcio de
Ari Gameplays and Juan
Ari Gameplays y Juan
Warnon will be announced well it was obvious you are saying it out
warnon bueno era obvio estáis diciendo
there in the chat damn it was obvious I don't
por ahí en el chat [__] era obvio yo que
know why because it was obvious to me  I've been
sé porque porque era obvio a mí me ha
surprised, damn, I've been surprised,
sorprendido [__] a mí me ha sorprendido
honestly. Let's see, I had no [ __ ]
la verdad A ver no tenía ni [__]
idea, I had no [ __ ]
idea no tenía ni [__]
idea, these people, well, this
idea estas personas bueno esta pareja
very famous couple, no, I would say surely
tan famosa no yo diría que seguramente
one of the most famous couples of
una de las parejas más famosas de los
Latin American streamers,
streamers latinoamericanos
well, they've divorced, okay, eh.
pues se han divorciado vale eh
Well, I don't know if they've divorced
Bueno no sé si se han divorciado
exactly or announced their divorce that is
exactamente o anunciar su divorcio que
in process, okay. I understand that they've
está en trámite vale Yo entiendo que se
divorced, eh. I understand that they've
han divorciado eh Yo entiendo que se han
divorced, but maybe it's in
divorciado pero a lo mejor está en
process, maybe it's in process. Okay,
trámite a lo mejor está en trámite Okay
but they have plans, I don't know if maybe
pero tienen planeado no sé si a lo mejor
this is going to change it. I understand that I don't
esto lo va a cambiar entiendo que no
understand that the fact that I
entiendo que esto el hecho de que yo
gave the exclusive because it was
haya dado la exclusiva porque se me ha
leaked to me and it reached me, well, I understand
filtrado y me ha llegado pues entiendo
that it doesn't change absolutely anything and that they are
que no cambia absolutamente nada y que
going to do it. In fact, Ari
lo van a hacer Igualmente de hecho Ari
posted
ayer puso
the following
la siguiente
post yesterday, let's see if I can get it, I don't know where I
publicación a ver si me llega no s dónde
had it yesterday ar posted the following post.
la tenía ayer ar puso la siguiente
Hello, hello, hello. How are you? Hey,
publicación Hola hola hola Cómo estás
tomorrow I'll turn on live and see you,
Oye ya mañana prendo directo y te veo
okay. And according to me, next week we
okay Y según yo ya la próxima semana ya
'll be a little more around
volvemos a estar un poco más por el
Setup again. That crazy girl, that crazy queue.  it
Setup esa loca esa cola loca no
worked I don't know what I don't know what
funcionaba No sé lo que no sé lo que es
the crazy glue is okay But what I think Is that
la cola loca vale Pero yo lo que creo Es
the Setup must have changed and
que que habrá cambiado el Setup
today he's obviously going to announce
y y hoy va a anunciar evidentemente
from his new Setup well, they're
desde su Setup nuevo pues pues este
going to communicate this divorce okay
divorcio lo van a comunicar vale
and the reasons and so on well obviously they
e los motivos y demás pues evidentemente
're private and no I haven't found out
son privados y no me no me he enterado
okay I haven't found out What are the
vale no me he enterado Cuáles son los
reasons it depends on how it looks it's
motivos depende de que como se vea es
bad news no if they don't get along together it's
mala noticia no si se llevan mal juntos
better that they separate Well yes Ramón I
mejor que se separen Pues sí Ramón estoy
completely agree with you yes yes it
Completamente de acuerdo contigo sí sí
's true yes it's true Ah that it's
que es verdad sí que es verdad Ah que es
a glue the glue is a
un pegamento la cola es un
glue let's see here I'm going to give a
pegamento a ver yo aquí voy a dar un
little my opinion obviously on
poco mi mi opinión evidentemente sobre
things that are public
cosas que son públicas
Okay for me in this
Ok yo en este
marriage Juan has swallowed a
matrimonio para mí Juan ha tragado
lot for me Juan has swallowed a lot okay
mucho para mí Juan ha tragado mucho vale
Why Because he's put up with a lot of
Por qué Porque ha aguantado montón de
things he's forgiven Well I don't know if
cosas ha perdonado Bueno no sé si
forgiven but yes that He's swallowed things that
perdonado pero sí que las Ha tragado
I wouldn't have swallowed okay he's
cosas que yo no hubiera tragado vale ha
forgiven things that are strong as you
perdonado cosas que que son fuertes como
know no and and besides that well he's
ya sabéis no y y además de eso pues
also lived with many things
también ha convivido con muchas cosas
that he didn't agree with on
con las que no estaba de acuerdo
the Lolly issue For example I
em el tema de Lolly Por ejemplo yo me
remember when  They made that
acuerdo cuando cuando le hicieron lo del
uncomfortable comment to him and he got
comentario aquel incómodo y él se
upset and said about the bed, okay, I mean, we
molestó y dijo lo de la cama vale o sea
could see absolutely clearly
ahí podíamos ver absolutamente clarísimo
in his body language that he had
en su lenguaje corporal que él realmente
never really accepted the idea of ​​his
nunca había aceptado el tema de que su
wife making that kind of content and
mujer hiciera ese tipo de contenidos y
all that, and that he just, well, I don't know if it was
demás no y que simplemente pues no sé si
because he was being modern or what, well, he swallowed
por dársela de moderno o qué Pues tragó
that. And that, you have to be
con eso Y eso el eso tienes que estar
very mentally prepared and you have to not care,
muy mentalizado y te tiene que dar igual
really, okay, for it to
de verdad vale para que para que
work in the relationship. And I'm
funcione en la relación
also telling you, uh, recently on one
e igualmente te digo eh hace poco en uno
of the
de los
newscasts, recently on one of the
noticieros hace poco en uno de los
newscasts, carlete carlete, behave yourself,
noticieros carlete carlete Pórtate bien
[ __ ], don't make those comments.
cabrón no pongas esos comentarios hace
Recently on one of the newscasts, we
poco en uno de los noticieros además
were also watching
estábamos Estuvimos viendo
that they were ordering a bed, do you
que que estaban encargando una cama os
remember on a newscast they were
acordáis que en un noticiero estaban
ordering a bed from a
encargando una cama a un a un sitio de
bed specialist site, so it's super powerful.
camas especialistas así s super potente
In fact, if I'm not mistaken,
De hecho si no me si no me equivoco
the work on
todavía no está ni terminada la obra de
the house they were building isn't even finished yet and they
la casa que se estaban construyendo y se
are building it. Because they are
están construyendo Porque se están
building an impressive house,
construyendo una casa impresionante que
I imagine that what they will do with it is
me imagino que lo que harán con eso será
sell it or  whatever it is it is a
venderlo o sea lo que sea es una
decision that I don't think is time consuming
decisión que no creo que venga de tiempo
okay I think it is a decision that
vale creo que es una decisión que ha ha
something has happened that has made him change his
pasado algo que que le ha hecho cambiar
mind and they have and they have decided to
de de opinión y han y han decidido
get divorced and in the next few hours on
divorciarse y en las próximas horas en
Juan's live it
el directo de Juan
will go Well I don't know if it's Juan's or Ari's
va Bueno no sé si de Juan o de Ari
because of course this message from Ari Let's see I do
porque claro este mensaje de Ari A ver
n't know if maybe they are going to do
no sé si a lo mejor lo van a hacer los
both live shows simultaneously I don't know but
dos directos simultáneos No lo sé pero
today they are both going to get together to
hoy se van a poner los dos juntos a
announce it Yes yes they were
comunicarlo Sí sí se estaban
building a house for years
construyendo una casa desde hace años
but a really good house also eh I
pero una casa de la [__] además eh o
mean a super exclusive house a brutal house
sea una casa super exclusiva una casa
imagine in their live shows the number of questions they will ask
imagina en sus directos la de preguntas
well let's see I imagine
que le harán bueno a ver yo me imagino
that everyone is now
que todo el mundo pues ahora está
thinking hate and in a gossip that has been
pensando odio y en un salseo que lleva
going on for many years But oh well
muchos años sucediendo Pero bueno
family I'll leave it there okay
familia Yo lo dejo por ahí vale
I hope things go well for them I mean I
Espero que les vayan bien las cosas o
hope they are for the best okay I mean
sea espero que sean para bien vale o sea
if they have divorced Well I wait to see
si se han divorciado Pues espero a ver
if they didn't get along and the love is gone and they did
si se llevaban mal y el amor se ha ido y
n't love each other anymore or maybe they argued or
ya no se quería o a lo mejor discutían o
whatever then I hope that this change Well
lo que sea pues espero que este cambio
in its  life, well, be it for the best,
Pues en su vida pues sea para bien
obviously not,
evidentemente no
eh. No, if you love goes away or you don't
eh No si tú el amor se va o tú no no te
get along with a person, well, it's obvious
llevas con una persona pues Es evidente
that you have to rebuild your life and that's it,
que tienes que rehacer tu vida y y ya
okay, if it was because one of the
está vale si ha sido porque uno de los
two has stopped loving the other, well, I'm
dos ha dejado de querer al otro pues
so sorry for the person
pues lo siento muchísimo por la persona
who is, what about And above all, I'm so sorry
que que tal Y sobre todo lo siento mucho
for both of them and for the family because these are
por los dos y por la familia porque son
very painful times and they're going to have to
momentos muy dolorosos y se van a tener
keep seeing each other because in the end they're still
que seguir viendo porque al final siguen
in the business world and in
en el en el mundo de los negocios y en
the Lore that they have, they continue
el y en el Lore que tienen siguen
collaborating and so on because they have a
colaborando y demás porque tienen una
series together. In fact, Juan, eh, now he
serie juntos De hecho Juan eh Ahora
has ama, not as president of the
tiene a ama no como presidenta de la
Annihilators. So I understand that they
aniquiladoras Así que entiendo que
will stay in contact and if they're going to be
seguirán en contacto y si van a ser el
that live together, I imagine that for
directo ese juntos me imagino que de
now we'll see, let's see as
momento ya veremos a ver cuando vaya
time goes by how
pasando el tiempo cómo va va dando la
things go. Okay,
cosa Vale
eh. Well, for now, they've ended well and they
Eh Pues de momento han acabado bien y se
're getting along. Javi, how did it come to you
están llevando bien Javi cómo te llegó
by mistake? He basically tells us because, let's
por error cuenta básicamente porque a
see, basically because
ver básicamente porque porque lo lo
some YouTubers from Mexico know about it, okay,
saben algunos youtubers de México vale
their whole circle knows about it and
todo el círculo de ellos lo sabe y y
well, one of the friends from Mexico.
pues pues uno de los amigos de México
Well, or  it practically reached me
Bueno o sea prácticamente me ha llegado
without any further ado it reached me they were
sin más me ha llegado se han descuidado
a little careless and it practically reached me
un poco y me ha llegado prácticamente
okay from there from Mexico they know it and and they
vale de allí de México lo saben y y me
come to me from there okay eh
vienen por ahí vale
I think that I think that from here in
eh yo creo que yo creo que de aquí de
Spain nobody knew eh still eh
España no lo sabía nadie eh todavía eh
I think that from here to Spain we were the
yo creo que de aquí a España hemos sido
first to know it and to
los primeros en saberlo y en y en
say it okay
decirlo vale
So I don't know what came across the news
Así que no sé qué os apareció la noticia
eh I don't know what came across the news
eh No sé qué os apareció la noticia
but maybe I got a little carried away
pero a lo mejor me he colado un poco
when I told you that the news was stronger
cuando os he dicho que era más fuerte la
than the breakup of
noticia que la que la ruptura de de
Auron and Gemita because I think that yes
auron y gemita porque yo creo que sí
no I think that obviously
no yo creo que evidentemente
this is a bigger news than the one
esto es una noticia más bomba que la
of Auron and
de que la de auron Y
Gemita so I'll tell you this afternoon the
gemita entonces ya os digo la tarde la
afternoon the afternoon
tarde la tarde de hoy Yo creo que va a
today I think it's going to be Auron announcing the breakup yesterday Auron suddenly cut off the live if you noticed how very unexpectedly he did a very short live Okay and he cut it off quickly because something was going on on Twitter and and
porque se estaba liando en Twitter y y
I think that Auron will confirm today the
yo creo que auron hoy confirmará la la
breakup the separation with Gemita I think
ruptura la separación con gemita creo
that  he's not going to throw it at gemita I do
que no le va a tirar a gemita Creo que
n't think he's going to say that gemita cheated on him
no va a decir que gemita lo ha engañado
and all that I don't think he's going to say
y todo eso creo que no lo va a decir
but I'm telling you By the way there's a lot of
pero os lo digo yo Por cierto hay muchas
speculation out there that if gref that
especulaciones por ahí de que si gref
if I don't know what a Random is I don't even know
que si no sé qué es un Random no sé ni
who it is okay it's a Random and and the issue
quién es vale es un Random y y el tema
of Juan Well it will be in the
de de Juan Pues será en el horario
Mexican schedule then at night okay
mexicano luego por la por la noche vale
then at the time that at the time that they
luego a la hora que a la hora que ellos
usually go live if I'm not
se suelen poner en directo que si no me
mistaken when we are
equivoco cuando nosotros estemos en
live at night Today I won't I
directo por la noche Yo hoy no me Yo hoy
won't go live at the salsería Today I
no me pondré en directo en la salsería
understand that I looked at telesalseo
Yo hoy entiendo que miré a telesalseo
because yesterday he couldn't do anything on
porque ayer no pudo hacer nada en
telesalseo and today either so
telesalseo y hoy tampoco así que
I will try to be on telesalseo today
intentaré hoy estar en telesalseo
I will try to be on telesalseo today Hey
intentaré estar hoy en telesalseo Oye
Thank you very much to all of you who
Muchísimas gracias a todos a los que os
have become members and super chat and
habéis hecho miembros y super chat y
those little things okay forgive me that they
esas cositas vale perdonarme que no
haven't sounded but it's that I don't know
hayan sonado pero es que no sé el Por
why I don't know why they haven't sounded it's
qué no sé por qué no han sonado est
configuring a little the the obs before it
configurando un poco el el obs antes
was better the  news Antonio had
de estuvo mejor la noticia Antonio habí
uploaded other people's content
subiendo contenido ajeno
and we'll see each other,
e nos vemos
okay, a kiss family and
nos vemos vale un beso familia y
thank you very much. See you later at
muchísimas gracias Nos vemos luego por
night on telesalseo, okay, handsome, bye
la noche en telesalseo vale guapos adiós
[Music]
[Música]